Cosmic bleeps,
Ready for space mission?
5 4 3 2 whoa whoa whoa whoa
Put on your space suit, put on your boots,
Strap in tight in your silver astronaut suits!
Check the bright buttons, red and green,
Coolest spaceship that you've ever seen!
Engines roaring, ready to ignite,
Flying up into the starry night!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, off we go!
Shining in the cosmic glow!
Flying past the moon, higher than high,
Little silver rocket in the big dark sky!
Look at Planet Mars, spinning around,
No noise in space, not a single sound!
Wave to Saturn with its shiny ring,
Hear the radio beep and sing!
Floating in zero gravity,
Catching little star-dust, you and me!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, off we go!
Shining in the cosmic glow!
Flying past the moon, higher than high,
Little silver rocket in the big dark sky!
Mission accomplished!
Touch down on Earth!
Bleep-bloop alien